easier.com 2009-09-19

# Easier.com Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

Your privacy is important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. 

**1\. Collection of Data.**

To use certain services on the Easier.com web site a user may be required to register. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for this purpose. 

**2\. Information We Collect.**

In general, you can browse the Easier.com web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, financial information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Easier.com web site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature. 

We automatically collect and process certain information based upon your use of the Easier.com web site. We use this information to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, serve and protect you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Easier.com web site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Easier.com web site or not), browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customised services and to help promote safer trading. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently while you are using the Easier.com web site. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session using the Easier.com web site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Easier.com web site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently while you are using the Easier.com web site. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Easier.com web site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**3\. Our Use of Your Information.**

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Easier.com web site, to resolve disputes, provide customer support, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customise the Easier.com web site content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Easier.com web site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information.**

Easier.com will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. 

By listing or advertising an item on the Easier.com web site you must provide a valid email address as a form of contact for the item. Your email address will not be revealed to another user unless you contact them. Although our pages are coded with robot exclusion headers, individuals and corporations may illegally attempt to automatically collect your email address from our web site. 

We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number are never disclosed to third party advertisers. 

We cannot ensure that all of your communications with Easier.com and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from the Easier.com web site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or communications with Easier.com will always remain private. 

**5\. Control of Your Password.**

You are responsible for all actions taken with your login and password, therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your Easier.com password to any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password or account has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

**6\. Editing or Deleting Your Login and Password.**

We offer you the ability to automatically review and change the information you submit to us by logging into the Easier.com web site and entering in the new information yourself. You can change your login and password, adverts and listings by going to the "My Classifieds" section on the Easier.com web site. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. 

**7\. Security**

Easier.com uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including encryption, "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. Easier.com treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorised access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorised access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**8\. Notice**

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.
